Guide to the Records of the Office of the Director of Student Affairs, University Heights RG.12.1
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of the Director of Student Affairs, University Heights
1896-1973
New York University Archives
New York University. University Heights
RG.12.1
15 Linear Feet in 30 manuscript boxes
This collection is made up of the papers of the Office of the Director of Student Affairs at New York University's University Heights campus from 1896 until 1973, when the campus closed. It includes records of various student organizations, events, and fraternities and sororities.
Access Restrictions
Material pertaining to individual student records may be restricted in accordance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). Please contact the Archives with specific questions regarding access to such records.
History of the Office of Student Affairs
New York University opened its University Heights campus in 1894. The Office of the Director of Student Affairs was in charge of housing for students as well as providing support for student groups and organizing student events. Overall, the office worked to enhance student life outside of the classroom. The office oversaw student clubs, such as academic and social fraternities and sororities, and events held for students like commencement. In the 1940s the director of the office was Alan Coutts, who was succeeded by former assistant dean of Yale College, Dr. Lewis M. Wiggin, in 1955. However, this collection comprises primarily the papers of the following two directors: Philip Price, who took the job in 1958, and Hans Hopf, who replaced Price following his death in 1969.
Arrangement
Records are arranged alphabetically by subject within four series:
Administrative Subject Files
Student Affairs
Clubs and Societies
Fraternities and Sororities
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of the records of the Office of the Director of Student Affairs at New York University's University Heights campus. Records include correspondence, proposals, and promotional material related to student events, such as Senior Class Night and commencement, as well as information on the construction and organization of the Gould Student Center. Minutes and election records are included for the Student Council as well as the Committee on Student Activities. There are also student organization papers for clubs and publications such as The Violet (yearbook), the Heights Young Republicans, and the Equestrian Club, among many other groups. Also found here are pledge lists and correspondence from several fraternities.
Student-administrator relationships.; Universities and Colleges -- Administration; Administrative records.; School yearbooks.; Fraternal organizations; Student newspapers and periodicals |z New York (State) |z New York.; Commencement ceremonies |z New York (State) |z New York |v Periodicals.; Correspondence.; Coutts, Alan; Wiggin, Lewis, Dr.; Price, Philip; Hopf, Hans; New York University. University Heights; Voorhis, Harold O.
- Series I: Administrative Subject Files
  - Ad Hoc Committee "To Review Dormitory Services and Food Plans", 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Affirmative Action, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Altschul House: Dedication, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Altschul House: Interfaith Council Correspondence, 1961-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Altschul House: Interfaith Council Minutes, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Altschul House: Kosher Kitchen, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Altschul House: Memoranda, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Altschul House: General Internal Correspondence of Philip Price, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Altschul House: Proposal for Communal Living, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Altschul House: Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Altschul House: Reports, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Altschul House: General Correspondence of Gordon Schaeffer, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Altschul House: Schedule of Activities, 1961-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Altschul House: Original Correspondence of Richard Van Wie, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Altschul House: General Correspondence of Tom Wahman, 1962-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Awards Dinner, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Career Seminar, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports, 1960-1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Awards and Prizes, 1959-1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Baccalaureate Services, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Baccalaureate Services and Senior Class Night Exercises, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Baccalaureate Services and Senior Class Night Exercises, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Baccalaureate Services, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Baer Browsing Room, 1961-1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Black Culture Week, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Black Student Affairs at the Heights, 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Black Student Affairs, General Information, 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Blood Drive and Blood Bank, 1962-1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Blood Drive, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Blueprint and Floor Plan, 1946,1955 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Building Use Policies, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: General, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Calendar of Events, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Calendar of Events, 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Campus Regulation Pamphlets, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Commission on Campus Disorders, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Reunion of Class of 1912 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1967, Correspondence General (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Coffee House, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1968, General Correspondence and Class Lists, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Student Life, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Committee for Improved Education Values, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Contracts, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Joint Committee on Discipline: Rules, Regulations, and Revisions, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Joint Faculty Commission on Dorms: Correspondence, 1961-1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Budget Matters, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Discipline, Joint Committee on: Correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Joint Faculty Committee on Dormitories: Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Joint Committee on Dormitories: Minutes, 1959-1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Drug Education, Committee on: Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Drug Education, Committee on: Printed Material, 1965-1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Educational Support Program Committee Proposal, 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - School of Engineering: General Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - School of Engineering: Newsletters, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - School of Engineering: Standing Committees, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - School of Engineering: Evening Division General Correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - School of Engineering: Evening Division Class Day Exercises, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - School of Engineering: Evening Division Student Council, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fund Raising Responses, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gould Chapel, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Gould Student Center Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Gould Student Center: General Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gould Student Center: Alterations and Maintenance, 1954-1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Gould Student Center: Annex, 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Gould Student Center: Blueprints and Designs, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Gould Student Center: Brochures, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Gould Student Center: Expansion, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Gould Student Center: Game Room, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Gould Student Center: Pictures, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gould Student Center: Plans, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Gould Student Center: Statistics, 1962-1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Gould Student Center 10th Anniversary, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, May 1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Hall of Fame Playhouse, 1954-1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - John F. Hatchett, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Heights Colleges Alumni Association, 1965-1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Heights Executive Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Heights Summer Community Program, 1969-1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Heights Summer Program Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Heights Summer Program Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Heights Summer Program Budget Information, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Heights Summer Program Donor Relations, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Heights Summer Program Draft Counseling, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Heights Summer Program Fundraising Responses, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Heights Summer Program Christian Fellowship, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Heights Summer Program: Newspapers, Publicity, and Photos, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Heights Summer Program Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Heights Summer Program Constitution of the Student Interfaith Council, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dean Brooke Hindle (University College), 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Housemother, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Housing and Dining Services, Occupancy Reports, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Inter-Dormitory Council Constitution, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Inter-Dormitory Council Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Inter-Dormitory Council Minutes, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Interfaith Council, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Inventory, 1963-1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Cultural Foundation, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Oliva Commission (Report on the Commission on Undergraduate Education), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Orientation, September 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Orientation, February 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Orientation, September 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Orientation, September 1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Orientation, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Palisades Handbook Controversy, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Protection, 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Publications, General Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Publications Board: Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Publications Board: Constitution, Regulations, and Procedures, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Publications Board Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Morton S. Rimer Award, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - R.O.T.C. SGB Report, 1969 Dec 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Safety Committee, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Senior Class Day Exercises, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Senior Class Day Exercises, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Senior Class Day Exercises, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Senior Class Night Exercises, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Senior Class Night Exercises, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Senior Class Night Exercises, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Senior Class Night Exercises, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Senior Class Night Exercises, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Senior Class Night Exercises, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Senior Class Night Exercises, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Senior Class Night Exercises, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Senior Class Night Exercises, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Senior Class Night Exercises, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Senior Prom, 1959-1968 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - South Bronx Tutorial Project, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Strike Information and Materials, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Student Activities Merger Committee, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Technology II, Dedication of, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - University Heights Council Minutes, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Voorhis Room, Dedication of, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Series II: Student Affairs
  - Student Council Constitution, Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1929-1930 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1931-1932 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1932-1933 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1933-1934 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1939-1940 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1940-1941 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Emergency Student Activities Committee Minutes, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Emergency Student Activities Committee Minutes, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Emergency Student Activities Committee Minutes, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Student Activities Committee Minutes, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Student Council Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Student Center Planning Committee, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Student Activities Correspondence, 1960-1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Student Activities Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Student Activities Membership, 1959-1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Student Activities Agenda, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Student Activities Constitution, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Student Activities Roster and Schedules, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Student Activities Sub Committee on Student Center Policy Board, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Student Activities Sub Committee on Heights Daily News Equipment, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Student Activities Sub Committee on Publications Board, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Student Activities Sub Committee on Hall of Fame Players, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Commission on Student Activities Sub Committee on Heights Graduate Student Council Representation of CSA, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Commission on Student Activities Minutes, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Student Activities Minutes, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Student Governing Board Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Student Governing Board Constitution and Bylaws, 1959, 1960, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Student Governing Board Women's Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Student Governing Board Government Reform Commission, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Student Government General Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Student Government Bylaws, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Student Government Student Senate, 1969-1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Student Government Bookstore Committee, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Student Government Budget and Finance Committee, 1960-1973 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Student Government Cafeteria Committee, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Student Government Calendar Committee, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Student Government Chapel Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Student Government Course Evaluation Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Student Government Curriculum Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Student Government Executive Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Student Government Joint Faculty Student Committee, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Student Government Library Committee, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Student Government Operations Committee, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Student Government Operations Committee Senators Elections, Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Student Government Operations Committee Senators, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Student Government Operation Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Student Government Parking Committee, Undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Student Government Protection Committee, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Student Government Public Service Committee, Undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Student Government Qualifications Committee, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Student Government Registration Committee, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Student Government Staff and Administrative Review Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Student Government Conduct, Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Student Government Heights Transit Control, 1960-1963 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Student Government Publicity Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Student Government Welfare Committee, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Student Center Policy Board Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Student Center Policy Board Constitution, 1959, 1963, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Student Center Policy Board Membership, 1964-1970 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Student Center Policy Board General Information, Undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Student Center Policy Board Rosters and Schedules, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Student Center Policy Board Calendar of Events, Undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Student Center Policy Board President, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Student Center Policy Board Treasurer, 1962-1966 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Student Center Policy Board Minutes, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Student Center Policy Board Committee Reports, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Student Center Policy Board Operations Committee, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Student Center Policy Board House Committee, 1960-1968 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Student Center Policy Board Ad Hoc Committee, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Student Union Board General Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Student Union Board Constitution, Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Student Union Board General Information, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Student Union Board President, 1969-1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Student Union Board Treasurer's Report, 1969-1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Student Union Board Minutes, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Student Union Board Minutes, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Student Union Board Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Student Union Board Billiards Committee, Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Student Union Board Coffeehouse, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Student Union Board Concerts Committee, Undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Student Union Board Creative Arts Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Student Union Board Film Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Student Union Board Lectures Commitee, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Student Union Board Publicity Committee, Undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Student Union Board Sub-Pub, Undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Student Union Board Special Events, Undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Series III: Clubs and Societies
  - Constitutions of Departmental Honor Societies, 1930-1960 (Box 19, Notebook 1)
  - Constitutions for Campus Societies, 1965-1970 (Box 19, Notebook 2)
  - Campus Societies, Membership Lists, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Notebook 3)
  - Alpha Phi Mu (Industrial Engineering), 1950-1958 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Beta Lambda Sigma (Biology), 1933-1961 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Chi Epsilon (Civil Engineering), 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Pershing Rifles (Air Science), 1962-1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Delta Phi Alpha (German), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Eta Kappa Nu (Electrical Engineering), 1958-1968 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Eta Kappa Omega (Economics), 1964-1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Green Room Honor Society (Dramatics), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - New York University Honorary Society, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Park Historical Society, 1958-1966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1964-1968 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Phi Sigma Alpha (Political Science), 1964-1968 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Pi Tau Sigma (Mechanical Engineering), 1958-1960 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Psi Chi (Psychology), 1939-1958 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Rho Tau Sigma (Radio and TV), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Scabbard and Blade (Military Science), 1956-1967 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Sigma Gamma Tau (Aeronautics/Astronautics), 1960-1964 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Sigma Pi Sigma (Physics), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Tau Kappa Alpha (Speech and Drama), 1963 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Adam Smith Economics Society, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Akiva Society, 1954, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - American Institute of Chemical Engineers, 1960-1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics, 1966, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - American Institute of Industrial Engineers, 1959-1969 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - American Institute of Metallurgical Engineers and American Society for Metals, 1960-1968 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - American Institute of Physics, 1960-1968 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - American Language Institute for International Students, 1962-1965 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - American Meteorological Society, 1960-1968 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - American Nuclear Society, 1960-1965 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - American Rocket Society, 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1933, 1960-1968 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Angel Flight/Arnold Air Society, 1955-1962 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Arab Student Club, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Armed Forces Communication and Electronics Association, 1959-1964 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Association for Computing Machinery, 1965-1966, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Art and Literary Society, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Association of the United States Army, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Beta Alpha Kappa House Plan, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Bowling League, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Bridge Club, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Brite House Plan, 1960-1964 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Children's Christmas Party, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 24)